Now, let's look at the second metric, which is recall.
现在 我们将学习第二个指标 召回率
Recall is the answer to the following question,
召回率用来回答以下问题
out of the points that are labeled positive,
在全部被标记为阳性的点中
how many of them were correctly predicted as positive?
有多少被正确的诊断出来为阳性？
So in the medical model, a recall is the answer to the following question,
因此 在医学模型中用召回率来回答以下问题
out of the sick patients,
在全部的实际患病的病人中
how many did we correctly diagnose as sick?
有多少被正确的诊断出有病?
So remember, precision was,
所以请记住 精度是
out of the patients were diagnosed as sick,
在所有被诊断为患病的人中
how many were actually sick?
有多少是真正的患者?
But recall is the opposite;
但是召回率与此相反；
out of the patients that are sick,
在所有真正的患者中
how many did we correctly diagnose as sick?
有多少被成功诊断出患病
It can be seen as a reach of the algorithm.
它可以看作是有以下算法的延申
How many of the positive points did I manage to catch?
我们成功捕获的真正的阳性点有多少？
The answer is calculated with this row.
答案是用这一行来计算
As we can see,
我们可以看到
this row catches a critical case labeled by an X,
这一行捕获了标记为X的关键情况
so we can see that recall is important in the medical model.
因此 我们可以看到 召回率在医学模式中很重要
Now to calculate recall,
现在计算召回率
we do the following;
我们做以下工作
from the 1,200 sick patients,
在全部1200个病人中
how many did we diagnose correctly?
我们成功诊断出的病人是多少？
That's 1,000 divided by 1,200,
1000除以1200
which is 83.3 percent.
结果是83.3%
This model better have a higher recall because we're trying to
医学模式需要有更高的召回率
correctly catch as many of the sick people as possible.
因为我们想尽可能多的诊断出的病人
Now in the email model,
在电子邮件模式中
the recall is defined similarly.
召回率的定义与之类似
It's calculated as follows;
它的计算过程如下
from the spam emails,
在全部的垃圾邮件中
how many of them do we correctly send to the spam folder?
我们正确检测出的垃圾邮件是多少？
The answer is in this row over here.
答案在这一行中
So we have 100 correctly sent to the spam folder divided by 270 total spam emails.
在全部270个的垃圾邮件中  我们检测出100个 所以100除以270
It's a low number. It's 37 percent.
这个数字很低是37%
But remember, we are worried about avoiding this X over here,
但请记住 我们是担心在这里（假阳性区）出现这个X
since we don't mind if we don't catch
我们不介意偶尔没有过滤掉一些垃圾邮件
all the spam emails as long as the ones we caught are spam.
但我们希望捕获到的垃圾邮件都是真正的垃圾邮件
So it's okay that this model has a low recall.
所以 我们可以容忍这个模型有较低的召回率
Now, let's do a similar exercise as before.
现在 让我们做一个和前面类似的练习
In this linear model over here,
这个线性模型的
what is the recall?
召回率是多少?
Enter your answer below.
请在下面输入你的答案